BASTIEN LAFALIZE

WEB DEVELOPER

Happy inhabitant of the city of Liège, **Junior Web Developer**. I always loved technology. Before that, I had several experiences as a specialized educator, in which I was able to develop certain qualities such as listening to the needs of others, patience, punctuality, ...

Passionate about **photography**, I think it can be a plus in the web development world, especially for the front-end.



TECH-SKILLS



SOFT-SKILLS

- Enthusiasm
- Perseverance
 - -

- Creativity
- Empathy
- Team-player
- Continuous learner

INFOS

- 9 0479/02.11.07 Rue Paradis 94 4000 Liège, Belgique
- bastienlafalize@gmail.com
- in LinkedIn : bastien-lafalize
- Github: bastlaf
- 😵 Codepen : @bastlaf
- https://bastlaf.github.io/CV-new/
- French: C2 English: B1
- Hobbies: photography, story of music, nature, ecology, video-games,...

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Liège - BeCode

2020-2021

- Learning web development, mainly in remote.
- Realization of solo and group projects (front-end and back-end).
- Realisation of personal projects.

Marche-en-Famenne - Mandabar

2017-2019 (student-job)

• Barman, room server

Achouffe - Brasserie de La Chouffe, salon de dégustation

2016-2017 (student-job + BSB certificate)

• Barman, room server

Achouffe - Petite-fontaine

2012-2015 (student-job

• Barman, room server

TRAINING

Liège - HECh Les Rivageois

2015 - 2019 (not completed)

 Bac, Educator Specializing in Psychoeducational Support

Liège - Helmo Ste-Marie

2014(not completed)

• First year in Business Informatics